

BRUNO CUEVAS

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEERING

in www.linkedin.com/in/brunomcuevas



brunocuevas.ml



bruno-cuevasāhotmail.com



+54 3489 691235

About Me

Since I was a child I have been curious and proactive, with a great capacity to establish relationships with others. These skills always led me to excel and learn, facing and overcoming all challenges. In terms of goals, I want society to benefit from my education and life experiences, hoping to inspire others along the way.

Education

Austral University (2019 - 2023)

Degree in Industrial Engineering - 8,74 (3,3 GPA)

Oriented on Mechatronics and Business Intelligences.

Dante Alighieri School (2013 - 2018) High School Diploma oriented in humanities - 9,13 (3,6 GPA)

Extracurricular Courses

Ted Talk - International Summit of Adaptative Leadership - Robotics and IT courses on Data Science

Technologies

















Projects and Experiences

2022 - Predictor

I have developed a web-app that predicts real estate prices using artificial intelligence models.

2021 - Beverage Dispenser

I built a beverage dispenser using industrial equipment and applying PLC programing skills.

2021 - Robotic Hand

Built a 3d-printed robotic hand controlled by IA, an App and a qlove.

2017 & 2018 - Piano Masterclass, Italy

I participated in two piano masterclasses in Italy, perfecting the Chopin's Ballade no 1 and his Revolutionary Etude.

Hobbies



Experience

IAE Business School (2021 - Present)

Research project with the aim of solving problems related to lack of capacity, by developing new commercial proposals and competitive advantages for the important multinational brand: Pernod Ricard.

Energy Institute - (2021 - Present)

Responsible for the exploratory analysis of Vaca Muerta data, seeking to develop reports that facilitate access to information and promote progress in the Energy area. I am also working to launch the institute website.

President of the 2019 Class - Industrial Engineering

Act within the personal environment and transform it for the better. Using leadership and communication skills I make decisions that benefit all parties equally.

Teacher

Austral University: Assistant Professor on Statistics/Algebra/Chemistry. Escuela Dante Alighieri: Calculus Teacher & Innovation Area. Piano teacher: Classical music since 2013. I participated in a piano masterclass in Vittorio Veneto, Italy.

Languages

English	
Italian	

Spanish

Recognitions

Austral's Research Congress: 3rd place (2021)

As a spokesperson of statistics cathedra, I introduced an educative data science project to predict results from high school math exams by using machine learning.

"Austral's Academic Excellence Scholarship" and "Galicia's Scholarship"

Galicia Bank and Austral University are investing in my academic career with a full tuition scholarship, allowing me access to highlevel education.

Winner of Dante Alighieri School "Honor Award 2018"

Over the course of six years, directives and professors had been evaluating high school students for this award. They have taken into account: proactivity, enthusiasm, perseverance, good disposition and the ability to establish good relationships with peers and superiors.